<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<learner><head sortkey="TR413*0100*2000*01">
  <candidate><personnel><language>French</language><age>21-25</age></personnel><score>35.0</score></candidate>
  <text>
     <answer1>
       <question_number>1</question_number>
       <exam_score>5.2</exam_score>
         <coded_answer>
          <p>Dear Mrs Ryan,</p>
          <p>I am delighted to <NS type="RV"><i>answer you back</i><c>reply</c></NS> to give you more <NS type="CN"><i>informations</i><c>information</c></NS> about me since I have won such a nice <NS type="RN"><i>price</i><c>prize</c></NS>.</p>
          <p>As I have already planned my holiday for August, I will only be available in July, after my exams.</p>
          <p>It would be nice to have a tent because I have never been camping and would like to try it, at least once.</p>
          <p>The list of activities that you have is very interesting so my choice was very difficult to make but I have finally decided to <NS type="FV"><i>chose</i><c>choose</c></NS> sailing because I have been sailing for five years now and enjoy it very much. My second choice is climbing because I have never climbed and would like to have a go at it.</p>
          <p>I do not have any idea of what the weather is like and what kind of clothes I should take. Also, I would like to know if it is better to exchange my money in England or in the USA.</p>
          <p>I hope you will be able to answer these questions.</p>
          <p>Yours sincerely</p>
         </coded_answer>
     </answer1>
     <answer2>
       <question_number>3</question_number>
       <exam_score>4.3</exam_score>
         <coded_answer>
          <p>Like most of the girls<NS type="MP"><c>,</c></NS> I enjoy shopping but it can be either a great <NS type="RN"><i>moment</i><c>event</c></NS> or a nightmare.</p>
          <p>What you expect when you go shopping, generally with a friend or two, is <NS type="FV"><i>wandering</i><c>to wander</c></NS> around and <NS type="FV"><i>looking</i><c>to look</c></NS> at everything. Having money and <NS type="FV"><i>be</i><c>being</c></NS> able to spend it <NS type="RT"><i>in</i><c>on</c></NS> anything you want is brilliant therefore you try to turn it <NS type="RT"><i>in</i><c>into</c></NS> an enjoyable <NS type="RN"><i>moment</i><c>experience</c></NS>.</p>
          <p>The nightmare starts when you find out that the items you like the most are also the most expensive. Then, you decide to wait for the <NS type="RN"><i>savings</i><c>sales</c></NS> but <NS type="AGA"><i>it</i><c>they</c></NS> <NS type="AGV"><i>is</i><c>are</c></NS> even worse as everybody <NS type="AGV"><i>want</i><c>wants</c></NS> to do their shopping at that time and the streets are so crowded you cannot even look for your favourite items.</p>
          <p>You are hot in the shops, feel annoyed and most of the time cannot find anything you <NS type="TV"><i>wanted</i><c>want</c></NS>.</p>
          <p>To conclude, I would say that to have a nice <NS type="RN"><i>moment</i><c>time</c></NS> shopping you had better <NS type="FV"><i>to save</i><c>save</c></NS> a lot of money and buy something as soon as you see it or be very patient.</p>
         </coded_answer>
     </answer2>
  </text>
</head></learner>
