<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<learner><head sortkey="TR891*0100*2000*02">
  <candidate><personnel><language>Japanese</language><age>21-25</age></personnel><score>38.00</score></candidate>
  <text>
     <answer1>
       <question_number>1</question_number>
       <exam_score>5.3</exam_score>
         <coded_answer>
          <p>Dear Mr Robertson,</p>
          <p>Thank you for organising the school trip <NS type="RT"><i>in</i><c>to</c></NS> London. I am really looking forward to participating in the programme, especially the visit to the National Art Gallery. However, I am writing to make a suggestion about the trip on behalf of all the students in my class.</p>
          <p>Could I suggest that you consider changing the programme? The London Fashion and Leisure Show is going to take place on 14th March in the Central Exhibition Hall in London. According to the advertisement I have seen, it is supposed to show the latest fashions, <NS type="MP"><i>leisure and sports wear</i><c>leisure- and sports-wear</c></NS>, <NS type="MP"><i>make up</i><c>make-up</c></NS> and hairstyles. It is also free to enter for students.</p>
          <p>It might be a good idea to fit this visit in in the afternoon on 14th March because I strongly believe that it would stimulate our interests in London so that we could study English with <NS type="FJ"><i><NS type="RJ"><i>strongest</i><c>greatest</c></NS></i><c>greater</c></NS> motivation. Even if we do not have enough time for shopping after the show, we will be able to go shopping <NS type="RT"><i>at</i><c>during</c></NS> <NS type="RD"><i>a</i><c>our</c></NS> free time on 15th March.</p>
          <p>I sincerely hope this letter will be of some help. I look forward to hearing from you.</p>
          <p>Yours sincerely,</p>
         </coded_answer>
     </answer1>
     <answer2>
       <question_number>2</question_number>
       <exam_score>5.1</exam_score>
         <coded_answer>
          <p>I believe that famous people, such as politicians and film stars, deserve to have a private life without journalists following them all the time for some reasons.</p>
          <p>First of all, they are the same as ordinary people even if they are treated as <NS type="AGN"><i>celebrity</i><c>celebrities</c></NS>. Therefore, they <NS type="UV"><i>should</i></NS> deserve to lead a normal life as we do.</p>
          <p>Secondly, <NS type="RP"><i>noone</i><c>no one</c></NS> has the right to <NS type="RV"><i>look at</i><c>snoop into</c></NS> anyone's private life even if they are journalists. Some people might say that we all have the right to know everything happening in the world as one of <NS type="RD"><i>the</i><c>our</c></NS> human rights. However, I think that they mix them up and that they should think about the right <NS type="RT"><i>of</i><c>to</c></NS> privacy.</p>
          <p>To sum up, famous people are the same as we are, and we all have the right to lead a private life and no right to <NS type="RV"><i>break into</i><c>intrude on</c></NS> their privacy. Therefore, I strongly believe that famous people deserve to have a private life without journalists following them all the time.</p>
         </coded_answer>
     </answer2>
  </text>
</head></learner>
