<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<learner><head sortkey="TR213*0100*2000*02">
  <candidate><personnel><language>Chinese</language><age>&lt;16</age></personnel><score>37.00</score></candidate>
  <text>
     <answer1>
       <question_number>1</question_number>
       <exam_score>5.3</exam_score>
         <coded_answer>
          <p>To Mr Robertson,</p>
          <p>Firstly, I would like to thank you for the programme that you <NS type="TV"><i>provided</i><c>have provided</c></NS>. It <NS type="TV"><i>was</i><c>is</c></NS> <NS type="MD"><c>a</c></NS> very good programme, especially the river trip to Greenwich, which I am sure the whole class <NS type="TV"><i>would</i><c>will</c></NS> enjoy.</p>
          <p>However, our class has spotted an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show and <NS type="UV"><i>would</i></NS> all wish to attend. It will be held at the Central Exhibition Hall in London on the 14th March. It will be from 10.00 till 7.00pm. The show will be about all the latest <NS type="FN"><i>fashion</i><c>fashions</c></NS>, leisure and sports wear, <NS type="MP"><i>make up</i><c>make-up</c></NS> and hairstyles. We would also not have to worry financially as it is free for students.</p>
          <p>This will be a great opportunity for us because we will be able to find out more about the people of London and their fashions and style<NS type="MP"><i> we</i><c>. We</c></NS> might also get a <NS type="RN"><i>change</i><c>chance</c></NS> to meet new people and <NS type="RV"><i>interest</i><c>interact</c></NS> with them. The whole class is also very excited about this fashion show and would really appreciate your giving them a <NS type="RN"><i>change</i><c>chance</c></NS> to go.</p>
          <p>I have a few <NS type="AGN"><i>suggestion</i><c>suggestions</c></NS> on how the programme could be changed to fit the London Fashion and Leisure Show in . We could do as planned for Monday and move going to the Science Museum from Tuesday to Wednesday afternoon. We would have to forgo the shopping as we might not have enough time and the exchange rate might be too high for us to do much shopping. We can<NS type="MP"><c>,</c></NS> however<NS type="MP"><c>,</c></NS> go and look around the shopping mall if we have time after the show.</p>
          <p>Lastly, I would be very grateful if you could give us your permission to go to the show. I hope you <NS type="TV"><i>would</i><c>will</c></NS> consider this matter. I look forward to hearing from you.</p>
          <p>Yours sincerely,</p>
         </coded_answer>
     </answer1>
     <answer2>
       <question_number>3</question_number>
       <exam_score>5.1</exam_score>
         <coded_answer>
          <p><NS type="RP"><i>Everyday</i><c>Every day</c></NS>, something changes and we become more modern<NS type="MP"><i> companies</i><c>. Companies</c></NS> use computers instead of books, <NS type="AGN"><i>dentist</i><c>dentists</c></NS> use modernized <NS type="RJ"><i>electrical</i><c>electric</c></NS> <NS type="FN"><i><NS type="RN"><i>item</i><c>tool</c></NS></i><c>tools</c></NS> instead of just a <NS type="MN"><c>pair of</c></NS> <NS type="IN"><i>plier</i><c>pliers</c></NS><NS type="RP"><i>, even</i><c>. Even</c></NS> homes are <NS type="RV"><i>effected</i><c>affected</c></NS>. From letters to emails, from gas stoves to electric stoves and microwaves<NS type="RP"><i>, but</i><c>. But</c></NS> we aren't just going to stop here are we? No, in the future, the present will be the past and <NS type="RD"><i>these</i><c>those</c></NS> things now new to <NS type="SX"><i>use</i><c>us</c></NS> will be old, outdated and changed.</p>
          <p>I see a very different home for us in the future. Most things will be computerised. We might even be using voice identification and fingerprints instead of keys. We <NS type="R"><i>an</i><c>can turn</c></NS> on and off lights with touch pads and remote <NS type="RN"><i>controllers</i><c>controls</c></NS>. We might even be able to open the door without <NS type="RV"><i>getting out</i><c>leaving</c></NS> <NS type="UT"><i>from</i></NS> the living room. Cameras will be something usual in every house instead of that little peephole in your door.</p>
          <p>Although all that may <NS type="RV"><i>change</i><c>happen</c></NS> our houses may be still the same. The rooms and <NS type="FN"><i>size</i><c>sizes</c></NS> should remain as <NS type="AGV"><i>it</i><c>they</c></NS> <NS type="AGV"><i>was</i><c>were</c></NS> and the living rooms and <NS type="RA"><i>all</i><c>everything</c></NS> may still be decorated in the same style. We might still <NS type="RV"><i>favour</i><c>like</c></NS> that old carpet and couch. The furniture should not change that much on the outside and the <NS type="RN"><i>amount</i><c>number</c></NS> of rooms should not change <NS type="RY"><i>too</i><c>either</c></NS>.</p>
          <p>In the future, every child might have a laptop. And instead of going to school, why not let school come to you? We will be learning at home using computers and <NS type="FN"><i>disc</i><c>discs</c></NS>. <NS type="TV"><i><NS type="MA"><i>Never</i><c>They never</c></NS> have</i><c>They will never have</c></NS> to leave the house or wake up so early. Another way our home could be different in the future is probably the <NS type="S"><i>utilitles</i><c>utilities</c></NS> we <NS type="TV"><i>are</i><c>will be</c></NS> using. We might not need maids to do housework anymore as they can easily be replaced with a robot, a machine, or something <NS type="R"><i>other</i><c>else</c></NS> with the same purpose.</p>
          <p>Our homes will still be the same in terms of the <NS type="RN"><i>kitchen</i><c>cuisine</c></NS><NS type="RP"><i>, it</i><c>. It</c></NS> will still be filled with vegetables and meat. This is because people won't <NS type="RV"><i>miss</i><c>give up</c></NS> the great taste of food<NS type="MP"><i> although</i><c>. Although</c></NS> it could be <NS type="S"><i>subsituted</i><c>substituted</c></NS> <NS type="RT"><i>to</i><c>with</c></NS> a vitamin pill or two.</p>
          <p>Lastly, I think that all <NS type="AGD"><i>this</i><c>these</c></NS> changes won't really be noticed as we change <NS type="RA"><i>it</i><c>things</c></NS> daily and slowly instead <NS type="MT"><c>of</c></NS> <NS type="S"><i>abruptedly</i><c>abruptly</c></NS>. People will be able to adjust and change with the times.</p>
         </coded_answer>
     </answer2>
  </text>
</head></learner>
