<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<learner><head sortkey="TR376*0100*2000*02">
  <candidate><personnel><language>Korean</language><age>26-30</age></personnel><score>21.00</score></candidate>
  <text>
     <answer1>
       <question_number>1</question_number>
       <exam_score>3.1</exam_score>
         <coded_answer>
          <p>Dear Mr. Robertson Thank you for your good programme for <NS type="MD"><c>the</c></NS> English class, especially <NS type="MC"><c>since</c></NS> it is well-organised and has many different places we can go and we can see. All of us in <NS type="MD"><c>the</c></NS> English class look forward to visiting these places. However, we'd like to ask about London Fashion and Leisure Show that we've seen an advertisement <NS type="MT"><c>for</c></NS> <NS type="RT"><i>on</i><c>in</c></NS> this <NS type="MP"><i>week</i><c>week's</c></NS> college newspaper. We would appreciate it if you could give us a chance to go there while we are visiting <NS type="UT"><i>in</i></NS> London. It should be a great opportunity for us because we can see the latest fashions, leisure and <NS type="RP"><i>sports wear</i><c>sportswear</c></NS>, <NS type="MP"><i>make up</i><c>make-up</c></NS> and <NS type="RP"><i>Hairstyles,</i><c>hairstyles.</c></NS> As you know, this year is our final year and most of us would like to get a job straight away after this course. We've been worried about our future career and we believe that we need some preparation for it such as <NS type="M"><c>advice about</c></NS> dress and hairstyle for an interview. And mostly, it should <NS type="MV"><c>be</c></NS> a great opportunity for the Art students who are attending English class. Most <NS type="UT"><i>of</i></NS> students in our class are studying Fashion <NS type="UT"><i>as</i></NS> full-time. Especially, it does not cost <NS type="MA"><c>anything</c></NS> at all for students. But the only problem <NS type="RT"><i>for</i><c>with</c></NS> the show is the date which is on Tuesday 14 March from 10.00 to 19.00. As we're considering your programme we're supposed to go <NS type="MT"><c>to</c></NS> <NS type="MD"><c>the</c></NS> Science Museum and shopping. We're thinking that we can go to these <NS type="AGN"><i>place</i><c>places</c></NS> the <NS type="UJ"><i>next</i></NS> following day. But Mr. Robertson, these <NS type="UD"><i>our</i></NS> suggestions <NS type="IV"><i>are depended</i><c>depend</c></NS> on your programme, we're just suggesting. Again we're so sorry that we <NS type="RV"><i><NS type="TV"><i>give</i><c>are giving</c></NS></i><c>are causing</c></NS> you <NS type="UD"><i>an</i></NS> <NS type="S"><i>inconvience</i><c>inconvenience</c></NS> <NS type="RT"><i>for</i><c>regarding</c></NS> your plan and thank you for considering us. We are <NS type="FV"><i>look</i><c>looking</c></NS> forward to hearing from you Yours sincerely,</p>
         </coded_answer>
     </answer1>
     <answer2>
       <question_number>3</question_number>
       <exam_score>2.3</exam_score>
         <coded_answer>
          <p>The Home of the Future.</p>
          <p>Have you ever thought about our future home?</p>
          <p>Living in a high building! But we could have <NS type="S"><i>everying</i><c>everything</c></NS> we want <NS type="UT"><i>to</i></NS>. Home might be a mixture with <NS type="S"><i>moden</i><c>modern</c></NS> styles and <NS type="MD"><c>a</c></NS> natural <NS type="RN"><i>view</i><c>appearance</c></NS> as well.</p>
          <p>These days a lot of <NS type="S"><i>contries</i><c>countries</c></NS> have been worried about <NS type="R">lands that can't have enough</NS> <NS type="RN"><i>place</i><c>space</c></NS> to build houses. The <NS type="S"><i>prises</i><c>prices</c></NS> for <NS type="FN"><i>lands</i><c>land</c></NS> are <NS type="UV"><i>getting</i></NS> increasing <NS type="U"><i>it's</i></NS> because of this <NS type="UN"><i>reason</i></NS>.</p>
          <p>So I think that the future home <NS type="R">could be considered this points</NS>. I mean most <NS type="UT"><i>of</i></NS> <NS type="AGN"><i>home</i><c>homes</c></NS> are going to be in a building like a flat. Maybe it is right <NS type="FV"><i>say</i><c>to say</c></NS> <NS type="UA"><i>that</i></NS> in a flat instead of a building. I believe there are a lot of high buildings now in Japan. Most of them are flats which have at <NS type="SX"><i>lest</i><c>least</c></NS> 20 Floors. It means <NS type="MD"><c>the</c></NS> Japanese are planning for the future home.</p>
          <p>But what <NS type="R"><i>my imagination</i><c>I imagine</c></NS> is that these flats'll have many functions such as offices, leisure centre, shopping centre even school. Because we are living <NS type="UT"><i>in</i></NS> <NS type="MD"><c>a</c></NS> <NS type="S"><i>computerlised</i><c>computerised</c></NS> life, <NS type="UC"><i>so</i></NS> we'll able to do most things at home or these flats'll have these places as well.</p>
          <p>But one more thing, I believe these flats'll have a park for people who'll be living in <NS type="RA"><i>there</i><c>them</c></NS>. And because it'll be a big building we'll <NS type="MV"><c>be</c></NS> able to see a <NS type="RJ"><i>whole</i><c>great</c></NS> view through the window.</p>
          <p>In conclusion, our future home will have a natural <NS type="RN"><i>view</i><c>appearance</c></NS> like <NS type="RY"><i>these days</i><c>today's</c></NS> <NS type="FN"><i>home</i><c>homes</c></NS> and give people a new technological home life.</p>
         </coded_answer>
     </answer2>
  </text>
</head></learner>
